https://www.paperpapers.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Domestic FREE* Ship for orders $39+ (48-contig) --> Learn more  -- 10% off over $100 with code 10p100
Menu
Toggle Nav
PAPERPaper by Size Small Cut Papers 8.27-x-11.69 (A4) 8-1/2-x-11 8-1/2-x-14 11-x-17 12-x-12 12-x-18 13-x-19 19-x-25 23-x-35 25-x-38 26-x-20 26-x-40 27-x-39 28-x-40 Small Cut Papers 8.27-x-11.69 (A4) 8-1/2-x-11 8-1/2-x-14 11-x-17 12-x-12 12-x-18 13-x-19 19-x-25 23-x-35 25-x-38 26-x-20 26-x-40 27-x-39 28-x-40Paper Thinner to Thicker GSM 64-90 (24/60T) GSM 104 (28/70T) GSM 118-120 (32/81T) GSM 124-162 (36T-60C) GSM 176 (65C) GSM-180-210 (121T-78C) GSM-216 (80C) GSM 220-255 (84-92C) GSM 260-270 (96-100C) GSM 284-298 (105-110C) GSM 300-380 (111-140C) GSM 432-850 (160-314C) GSM 64-90 (24/60T) GSM 104 (28/70T) GSM 118-120 (32/81T) GSM 124-162 (36T-60C) GSM 176 (65C) GSM-180-210 (121T-78C) GSM-216 (80C) GSM 220-255 (84-92C) GSM 260-270 (96-100C) GSM 284-298 (105-110C) GSM 300-380 (111-140C) GSM 432-850 (160-314C)Flat and Folded Cards Flat Cards Flat Text Folded Cards Flat Cards Flat Text Folded CardsPaper by Type Black Paper Bright Paper Cardstock Paper Cotton Paper Deckled Edge Paper Fiber Paper Linen Paper Metallic Paper Parchment Paper Recycled Paper Text Weight Paper Translucent Paper Black Paper Bright Paper Cardstock Paper Cotton Paper Deckled Edge Paper Fiber Paper Linen Paper Metallic Paper Parchment Paper Recycled Paper Text Weight Paper Translucent PaperPaper by Size Small Cut Papers 8.27-x-11.69 (A4) 8-1/2-x-11 8-1/2-x-14 11-x-17 12-x-12 12-x-18 13-x-19 19-x-25 23-x-35 25-x-38 26-x-20 26-x-40 27-x-39 28-x-40 Small Cut Papers 8.27-x-11.69 (A4) 8-1/2-x-11 8-1/2-x-14 11-x-17 12-x-12 12-x-18 13-x-19 19-x-25 23-x-35 25-x-38 26-x-20 26-x-40 27-x-39 28-x-40Paper Thinner to Thicker GSM 64-90 (24/60T) GSM 104 (28/70T) GSM 118-120 (32/81T) GSM 124-162 (36T-60C) GSM 176 (65C) GSM-180-210 (121T-78C) GSM-216 (80C) GSM 220-255 (84-92C) GSM 260-270 (96-100C) GSM 284-298 (105-110C) GSM 300-380 (111-140C) GSM 432-850 (160-314C) GSM 64-90 (24/60T) GSM 104 (28/70T) GSM 118-120 (32/81T) GSM 124-162 (36T-60C) GSM 176 (65C) GSM-180-210 (121T-78C) GSM-216 (80C) GSM 220-255 (84-92C) GSM 260-270 (96-100C) GSM 284-298 (105-110C) GSM 300-380 (111-140C) GSM 432-850 (160-314C)Flat and Folded Cards Flat Cards Flat Text Folded Cards Flat Cards Flat Text Folded CardsPaper by Type Black Paper Bright Paper Cardstock Paper Cotton Paper Deckled Edge Paper Fiber Paper Linen Paper Metallic Paper Parchment Paper Recycled Paper Text Weight Paper Translucent Paper Black Paper Bright Paper Cardstock Paper Cotton Paper Deckled Edge Paper Fiber Paper Linen Paper Metallic Paper Parchment Paper Recycled Paper Text Weight Paper Translucent PaperENVELOPESNeed
size help?
Envelope Size Chart
A-Size Envelopes A1 A2 A6 A7 A8 A9 A10 A1 A2 A6 A7 A8 A9 A10Baronial Envelopes 4 Bar 5 1/2 Bar 6 Bar 7 Bar / Lee 4 Bar 5 1/2 Bar 6 Bar 7 Bar / LeeBooklet-Catalog EnvelopesCommercial Envelopes No 6 1/4 No 6 3/4 No 7 - Monarch - No 7 3/4 No 9 No 10 No 11 and higher No 6 1/4 No 6 3/4 No 7 - Monarch - No 7 3/4 No 9 No 10 No 11 and higherShipping EnvelopesSquare EnvelopesMini EnvelopesSpecialty Envelopes Clasp Envelopes Deckled Edge Envelopes Foil Lined Envelopes Inner/Outer Envelopes Mini Envelopes Peel to Seal Envelopes Security Tint Envelopes Window Envelopes Clasp Envelopes Deckled Edge Envelopes Foil Lined Envelopes Inner/Outer Envelopes Mini Envelopes Peel to Seal Envelopes Security Tint Envelopes Window EnvelopesCheap EnvelopesShipping Supplies
Envelopes by SizeNeed
size help?
Envelope Size Chart
A-Size Envelopes A1 A2 A6 A7 A8 A9 A10 A1 A2 A6 A7 A8 A9 A10Baronial Envelopes 4 Bar 5 1/2 Bar 6 Bar 7 Bar / Lee 4 Bar 5 1/2 Bar 6 Bar 7 Bar / LeeBooklet-Catalog EnvelopesCommercial Envelopes No 6 1/4 No 6 3/4 No 7 - Monarch - No 7 3/4 No 9 No 10 No 11 and higher No 6 1/4 No 6 3/4 No 7 - Monarch - No 7 3/4 No 9 No 10 No 11 and higherShipping EnvelopesSquare EnvelopesMini EnvelopesSpecialty Envelopes Clasp Envelopes Deckled Edge Envelopes Foil Lined Envelopes Inner/Outer Envelopes Mini Envelopes Peel to Seal Envelopes Security Tint Envelopes Window Envelopes Clasp Envelopes Deckled Edge Envelopes Foil Lined Envelopes Inner/Outer Envelopes Mini Envelopes Peel to Seal Envelopes Security Tint Envelopes Window EnvelopesCheap EnvelopesShipping Supplies
Envelopes by SizeLabelsBrands2pBasicsArturoAstrobrightsAstroparcheBasis ColorsBrown Bag KraftCanaletto TexturedClassic Crest and Linen Natural White Solar White Natural White Solar WhiteColor Copy & OptionsCougarCrane 100% Cotton Crest Lettra Crest LettraCrush
CT TranslucentCurious Collection Curious Metallics Curious Skin Curious Metallics Curious SkinDeckled Edge Strathmore DurotoneEarthchoiceEnvironmentExactExtract Eco-Friendly (CupCycled)FAV ShimmerGlitter PaperHuskyKraft-toneLoop & ViaLynxNeenah 100% Cotton Blush Mint Blush MintOpaqueOtherParchtone
Aged Top Pick! Gunmetal (Gray) Natural White Aged Top Pick! Gunmetal (Gray) Natural WhitePlikePoptone ColorsRemakeRollandRoyal SundanceSavoy 100% CottonShine Metallic PapersSpeckletoneStardream MetallicSuperfine Softwhite Ultrawhite White SF Softwhite Ultrawhite White SF-- Closeout --Cocoa Kraft CloseoutKeaykolour Closeout2pBasicsArturoAstrobrightsAstroparcheBasis ColorsBrown Bag KraftCanaletto TexturedClassic Crest and Linen Natural White Solar White Natural White Solar WhiteColor Copy & OptionsCougarCrane 100% Cotton Crest Lettra Crest LettraCrush
CT TranslucentCurious Collection Curious Metallics Curious Skin Curious Metallics Curious SkinDeckled Edge Strathmore DurotoneEarthchoiceEnvironmentExactExtract Eco-Friendly (CupCycled)FAV ShimmerGlitter PaperHuskyKraft-toneLoop & ViaLynxNeenah 100% Cotton Blush Mint Blush MintOpaqueOtherParchtone
Aged Top Pick! Gunmetal (Gray) Natural White Aged Top Pick! Gunmetal (Gray) Natural WhitePlikePoptone ColorsRemakeRollandRoyal SundanceSavoy 100% CottonShine Metallic PapersSpeckletoneStardream MetallicSuperfine Softwhite Ultrawhite White SF Softwhite Ultrawhite White SF-- Closeout --Cocoa Kraft CloseoutKeaykolour CloseoutShop Color
Black Black Text Paper Black Card Stock Black Envelopes Black Text Paper Black Card Stock Black Envelopes Blue Blue Text Paper Blue Card Stock Blue Envelopes Blue Text Paper Blue Card Stock Blue Envelopes Brown Brown Text Paper Brown Card Stock Brown Envelopes Brown Text Paper Brown Card Stock Brown Envelopes Burgundy Burgundy Text Paper Burgundy Card Stock Burgundy Envelopes Burgundy Text Paper Burgundy Card Stock Burgundy Envelopes Coral Coral Text Paper Coral Card Stock Coral Envelopes Coral Text Paper Coral Card Stock Coral Envelopes Gold Gold Text Paper Gold Card Stock Gold Envelopes Gold Text Paper Gold Card Stock Gold Envelopes Gray Gray Text Paper Gray Card Stock Gray Envelopes Gray Text Paper Gray Card Stock Gray Envelopes Green Green Text Paper Green Card Stock Green Envelopes Green Text Paper Green Card Stock Green Envelopes Orange Orange Text Paper Orange Card Stock Orange Envelopes Orange Text Paper Orange Card Stock Orange Envelopes Pink Pink Text Paper Pink Card Stock Pink Envelopes Pink Text Paper Pink Card Stock Pink Envelopes Purple Purple Text Paper Purple Card Stock Purple Envelopes Purple Text Paper Purple Card Stock Purple Envelopes Red Red Text Paper Red Card Stock Red Envelopes Red Text Paper Red Card Stock Red Envelopes Silver Silver Text Paper Silver Card Stock Silver Envelopes Silver Text Paper Silver Card Stock Silver Envelopes Yellow Yellow Text Paper Yellow Card Stock Yellow Envelopes Yellow Text Paper Yellow Card Stock Yellow Envelopes Off-White Off-White Text Paper Off-White Card Stock Off-White Envelopes Off-White Text Paper Off-White Card Stock Off-White Envelopes White White Text Paper White Card Stock White Envelopes White Text Paper White Card Stock White EnvelopesMixed Mixed Text Paper Mixed Card Stock Mixed Envelopes Mixed Text Paper Mixed Card Stock Mixed EnvelopesTranslucent Translucent Text Paper Translucent Card Stock Translucent Envelopes Translucent Text Paper Translucent Card Stock Translucent Envelopes
Business BulkBulk PaperBulk EnvelopesFolio / Full-Size PapersPopular by Industry Restaurants Letterpress Restaurants LetterpressBulk PaperBulk EnvelopesFolio / Full-Size PapersPopular by Industry Restaurants Letterpress Restaurants LetterpressTry-Me Packs Top Pick Sample Packs Variety Packs Sample Packs Variety PacksDIYPapers for DIY Projects Card Makers Paper Flowers Paper Crafting (General) Card Makers Paper Flowers Paper Crafting (General)Paper for LIA ProjectsPaper by the SheetPapers for DIY Projects Card Makers Paper Flowers Paper Crafting (General) Card Makers Paper Flowers Paper Crafting (General)Paper for LIA ProjectsPaper by the SheetSave on ClearanceServices Help
Account
Home
Privacy and Cookie Policy
Privacy and Cookie Policy
This is the web site of  PAPER-PAPERS LLC / PaperPapers / PaperPapers.com(former and alias business names P A Publishing & Paper Supplies / Paper - Papers LLC / Paper-Papers / Paper-Papers.com)CONTACT INFORMATION:6000 Carlson Ave., Portage, IN 46368Phone: (219) 764-1000
What Information We Collect From You: For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, browser agent, operating system, whether the consumer has visited our site before, but not the customer's e-mail address.We collect aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, as well as information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. The information we collect is only used to improve the content of our Web page and to notify consumers about special events and promotions. We do not sell consumer information to outside companies.How We Use "Cookies": We use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart. We also record past activity at our site in order to provide better service when visitors return.Reasons We Might Contact You: By default, we do not send our users any unsolicited email. We only send notifications of product updates, etc., if a user has specifically requested this information. The choice of whether or not to receive these notifications can be changed at any time by logging into your account "customer login".  If you have trouble with login, please call us.
This privacy policy sets out how this website (hereafter "the Store") uses and protects any information that
you give the Store while using this website. The Store is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.
Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then
you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. The Store may change
this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure
that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service,
and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we
think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.
We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website
according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or
disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and
secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive.
Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit
a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application
can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about
your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page
traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for
statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find
useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you,
other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting
to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links
to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website.
Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst
visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.
You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate
that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes,
you may change your mind at any time by letting us know using our Contact Us information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission
or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information
about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998.
A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email us this
request using our Contact Us information.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete,
please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address.
We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
Cookie Name
Cookie Description
FORM_KEY
Stores randomly generated key used to prevent forged requests.
PHPSESSID
Your session ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to view and edit their orders.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history, if you have asked for this.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
MAGE-CACHE-SESSID
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE-SECTION-INVALIDATION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-TIMEOUT
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
SECTION-DATA-IDS
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
PRIVATE_CONTENT_VERSION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
X-MAGENTO-VARY
Facilitates caching of content on the server to make pages load faster.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-FILE-VERSION
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-STORAGE
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
All rights reserved to Paper-Papers LLC - Copyright © 1994 - 2020
